Aleksander Fret

tel.: 605 768 401

e-mail: aleksander.fret@op.pl www: aleksander.fret.com.pl

GitHub: www.github.com/alemikolo

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aleksander-fret



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Front-End Developer Creating applications and web sites using modern front-end

technologies, like JS ES6, React, Redux, Webpack...,

ability to use some of the back-end technologies – PHP and

MySQL,

designing user interfaces (big experience in fhe field of

graphics, interest in UI UX).

Graphic Designer and Cartographer

Extensive editorial practice – designing of publications, DTP,

broad qualifications in the field of graphics software,

Big experience in making various maps.

EXPERIENCE

Sandstream Development 01/2019–now: stanowisko Front-End Developer.

Personal website 09/2018: www.aleksander.fret.com.pl – my online CV. Main

technologies: ES6, React, SASS, PHP.

Udacity 11/2017–08/2018 (student): www.pixel-art-maker.fret.com.pl,

www.memorygame.fret.com.pl, www.arcadegame.fret.com.pl,

www.amusementparks.fret.com.pl.

Eko-Graf 10/2008–01/2019: Cartographer – Map Editor. Duties: designing

of graphic layouts and covers, editorial and cartographic tasks, DTP, creating of advertising materials, preparing for printing.

WilMat 10/2016: www.wilmat.com.pl.

Personal websites 07/2015: www.psychoterapia.fret.com.pl.

01/2015: www.ewa.fret.com.pl.

Others 11/2012: Via Mercatorum, website, logo, advertising leaflet...

04/2007-07/2008: SeaStar, Cartographer,

11/2005–12/2006: Nowa Era, Author: *Statistical tables*, 09/2004–03/2005: Wydawnictwo Marek Rożak, Cartographer.

EDUCATION

Udacity 11.2017–08.2018: Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree

Program (scholarship from Google).

Certain courses and trainings React 16 – the complete guide; The Complete Sass & SCSS Course; PHP – developing CMS; PHP, MySQL, JS.

University of University of University of University of Wroclaw 10.1999–07.2005: bachelor's degree in *Geography*, master's degree in *Geography*, specialization in *Cartography*.

Qualifications

Programming

JS ES6, OOP, React, Redux, JQuery, SASS, CSS, HTML, RWD, accessibility, SEO, PHP, MySQL, Twig, Webpack, Gulp, Git.

Graphics software

CorelDRAW, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Photo-Paint.

Others

English language (b1), Global Mapper.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Award in the competition organized by Ministry of Transport and Construction for master thesis *Atlas regional-ny województwa łódzkiego*.

III prize for "[...] modern editorial style, usability [...]", Wrocław – przewodnik (J. Czerwiński, Eko-Graf), XX Ogólnopolski Przegląd Książki Krajoznawczo-Turystycznej. Scope of work: graphic design and creation, DTP.

PERSONAL TRAITS

Creative, with attention to detail, reliable, responsible, strongly involved.

INTERESTS

Playing the guitar, listening to the music, board games, fantasy literature, games and films, football, mountain hiking, listening to the Trojka radio channel.

I hereby give consent for my personal data to be processed for the purposes of recruitment, in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act dated 29.08.1997 (uniform text: Journal of Laws of the Republic of Poland 2002 No 101, item 926 with further amendments).